Comstock Park, MI. Comstock Park Congregational Church records, 1888-2021.
Congregational Library & Archives
- Financial records, 1923 2000; 1923-2000; 28 Folders
  - Receipts and disbursements, 1946 1950; 1946-1950 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Building Fund subscribers, 1946 1949; 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Secretary reports, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Trustees and Building Committee, 1948 1951; 1948-1951 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's Accounts, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Church finances, 1950 1964; 1950-1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1955 1959; 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Financial statements for members, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer's report, 1960 1961; 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Michigan Non-profit Corporation reports, 1960 1969; 1960-1969 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Treasurer's report, 1962 1963; 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer's report, 1964 1966; 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Church finances, 1964 1975; 1964-1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bi-Annual Parsonage Inspection, February 13, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Budget records, 1970 1979; 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Michigan Non-profit Corporation reports, 1971 1979; 1971-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Michigan non-profits corporation reports, 1980 1983; 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Letters and notes related to church finances, 1981 1984; 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Meeting notes about the Parsonage, May 16, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Benevolence Committee records, 1982 1985; 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Letters and notes related to church finances, 1985 1989; 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Donation in the name of Zella Mutchler, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Gertrude Westover building fund, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Joseph Rypma building fund, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Balance sheets, 1990 1994; 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Donation Thank-You Letter, November 27, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 26)